Can't get the monkey off your back?
無法擺脫你背上的猴子嗎？
Then put it in your mouth with Monkey Shine Beer.
然後和Monkey Shine啤酒一起放進嘴裡。
Monkey Shine Beer, cause it's a jungle out there.
Monkey Shine 啤酒，因為那裡是叢林。
That commercial always makes me so sad.
那則廣告總是讓我如此悲傷。
Yeah, but then the guy opens his beer and those girls run at
是的，但是那傢伙開啟啤酒，那些女孩就跑過來
him.
他。
So, everything seems to work out okay.
所以，一切似乎都很順利。
I meant because the monkey in it reminds me of Marcel.
我的意思是因為裡面的猴子讓我想起了馬塞爾。
I can see that, cause they both have those big brown eyes and,
我看得出來，因為他們都有棕色的大眼睛，
you know, the little pouty chin.
你知道的，那個微翹的下巴。
And the fact that they're both monkeys.
事實上他們都是猴子。
Sometimes I wonder if I did the right thing, you know, giving him
有時我想知道我是否做了正確的事，你知道，給他
away.
離開。
Well, Ross, you had to.
好吧，羅斯，你必須這麼做。
I mean, he was humping everything in sight.
我的意思是，他把眼前的一切都搞砸了。
I mean, I have a Malibu Barbie who will no longer be wearing
我的意思是，我有一個不再穿著的馬里布芭比娃娃
white to her wedding.
白色到她的婚禮。
Remember when sometimes she'd borrow your hat and when you got it back
還記得有時她會借你的帽子以及你什麼時候把它拿回來嗎
there'd be little monkey raisins in it?
裡面會有小猴子葡萄乾嗎？
God, he loved that joke.
天哪，他喜歡這個笑話。
Yeah, well, sure, when he did it, it was funny.
是的，嗯，當然，當他這麼做的時候，很有趣。
When I did it to my boss's hat, all of a sudden I
當我對著老闆的帽子這麼做時，突然我
had this big attitude problem.
有這麼大的態度問題。
So no one told you life was gonna be this way Your job's
所以沒有人告訴你生活會是這樣 你的工作
a joke, you're broke, your love life's the old way It's like you're
開玩笑，你破產了，你的愛情生活還是老樣子，就像你
always stuck in second gear But when it hasn't been your day or
總是卡在第二檔但是當這不是你的日子或
week or month Or even all your years But I'll be there for
一週或一個月甚至你所有的歲月但我會在那裡
you When the rain starts to pour Hey,
你當雨開始傾盆而下時嘿，
hey, check it out, guess what I got.
嘿，檢查一下，猜猜我得到了什麼。
Rhythm?
韻律？
No, my first fan mail.
不，這是我的第一封粉絲來信。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Dear Dr. Ramore, know that I love you and would do anything to
親愛的拉莫爾博士，請知道我愛你，並且會盡一切努力
have you.
你。
Oh, gosh, you're not some secret admirer.
哦，天哪，你不是什麼秘密崇拜者。
Erica Ford.
艾麗卡·福特。
Ew, wait.
呃，等等。
P.S. Enclosed, please find 14 of my eyelashes.
附：隨信附上，請尋找我的 14 根睫毛。
You know, in crazy world, that means you're married.
你知道，在瘋狂的世界裡，這意味著你已經結婚了。
This wasn't addressed to days of our lives, this came to your apartment.
這不是針對我們生活中的日子，而是針對您的公寓。
There's no stamp on it, this woman was in our building.
上面沒有印章，這個女人就在我們大樓裡。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I got my very own stalker.
我有自己的跟蹤狂。
Hey, you know, you are so lucky, I have to share mine with
嘿，你知道，你太幸運了，我必須與大家分享我的幸運
a bunch of guys down at work.
一群人正在上班。
Okay, Joey, remember when we talked about good thing, bad thing?
好吧，喬伊，還記得我們談論過好事和壞事嗎？
This is a bad thing.
這是一件壞事。
Hey, guys.
嘿，夥計們。
Hey.
嘿。
Where are you off to, Trav and Jake?
特拉夫和傑克，你們要去哪裡？
Well, there's this paleontology conference in L.A., so I figured I'd go
嗯，洛杉磯有一個古生物學會議，所以我想我應該去
and then drive down to the zoo and surprise Marcel.
然後開車去動物園給馬塞爾一個驚喜。
You know, I think you will be surprised, till he realizes he's a
你知道，我想你會感到驚訝，直到他意識到他是一個
monkey.
猴。
And, you know, isn't capable of that emotion.
而且，你知道，他沒有能力表達這種情感。
Oh, Phoebe, that really cute guy is here again.
哦，菲比，那個可愛的傢伙又來了。
Oh, oh, okay.
哦，哦，好吧。
So, everyone, pretend like I'm telling you a story, okay?
那麼，大家假裝我在跟你講故事，好嗎？
And it's really funny, so everyone just laugh.
而且真的很有趣，所以大家都笑了。
Now.
現在。
I know, I know.
我知道，我知道。
Hello.
你好。
Hi.
I'm Rob Donan.
我是羅布·多南。
Hi, Rob Donan.
嗨，羅布·多南。
I don't know anything about music, but I think you're really, really great.
我對音樂一無所知，但我覺得你真的真的很棒。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Anyway, I schedule performers for the children's libraries around the city, and
無論如何，我都會為全市的兒童圖書館安排表演者，並且
I was just thinking, have you ever thought about playing your songs for
我只是在想，你有沒有想過為你播放你的歌曲
kids?
孩子們？
Oh, I would love to have kids.
哦，我很想有孩子。
Hear, hear the, hear me play the songs that I will write for
聽，聽，聽我演奏我將為之寫的歌曲
them.
他們。
Hey, what do you want to do for dinner?
嘿，晚餐你想做什麼？
Well, we could just stay in and cook for ourselves.
好吧，我們可以留在家裡自己煮飯。
Hello.
你好。
It's Erica.
是艾麗卡。
The stalker.
跟蹤狂。
Never mind, it's open.
沒關係，已經開放了。
Yes, hitting her with a frying pan is a good idea.
是的，用煎鍋打她是個好主意。
We might want to have a backup plan, though, just in case she
不過，我們可能需要一個備用計劃，以防萬一她
isn't a cartoon.
不是卡通。
Let's get out of here.
我們離開這裡吧。
The one time they're not home.
有一次他們不在家。
Okay, okay.
好吧，好吧。
We'll just leave, and when we pass her on the stairs, she won't
我們就走吧，當我們在樓梯上經過她時，她不會
know it's me, because we never met.
知道是我，因為我們從未見過面。
That's how radio stars escape stalkers.
這就是廣播明星躲避跟蹤者的方法。
She's coming.
她來了。
It's me.
這就是我。
This is it.
就是這樣。
This is how we're going to die.
我們就是這樣死去的。
Ready?
準備好？
Wait, wait, wait.
等等，等等，等等。
Erica.
艾麗卡。
Mr. Geller?
蓋勒先生？
Yes, hi.
是的，嗨。
Hi, Dean Lipson, zoo administrator.
你好，迪恩·利普森，動物園管理員。
I was told you had a question.
我聽說你有一個問題。
Well, I, uh, I can't seem to find the monkey I donated last
嗯，我，呃，我好像找不到我上次捐獻的猴子了
year.
年。
He's a capuchin.
他是捲尾猴。
Answers to the name Marcel.
馬塞爾這個名字的答案。
Ah, I'm afraid I have some bad news.
啊，恐怕我有一些壞訊息。
Marcel has passed on.
馬塞爾已經去世了。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
What happened?
發生了什麼事？
Well, he got sick, and then he got sicker, and then he got
好吧，他病了，然後病得更重，然後他得了
a little better, but then he died.
好一點了，但後來他死了。
I can't believe this.
我簡直不敢相信這一點。
I'm sorry, Mr. Geller, but, you know, there's an old saying.
對不起，蓋勒先生，但是，你知道，有句老話。
Sometimes monkeys die.
有時猴子會死。
It's not a great saying, but...
這句話不是什麼好話，但…
it certainly is fitting today.
這在今天當然是合適的。
Well, you know, someone should have called me.
嗯，你知道，應該有人打電話給我。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
Look, I know this can't bring him back, but here, it's just a
聽著，我知道這不能讓他回來，但在這裡，這只是一個
gesture.
手勢。
Zoo dollars?
動物園幣？
Yes, and come see the bird show at four.
是的，四點鐘來看鳥類表演。
The macaws wear hats.
金剛鸚鵡戴著帽子。
Well, it's a lot cuter if your monkey hasn't just died.
嗯，如果你的猴子沒有死的話那就可愛多了。
I'm sorry.
對不起。
I know.
我知道。
I can't believe Joey's having lunch with his stalker.
我不敢相信喬伊正在和他的跟蹤者共進午餐。
What is she like?
她是什麼樣的人？
Well, you remember Kathy Bates in Misery?
嗯，你還記得《苦難》中的凱西·貝茨嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Well, she looks the exact opposite of that.
嗯，她看起來恰恰相反。
And she's not crazy?
而且她沒瘋？
Oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
She's a total whack job.
她真是個糟糕的工作。
Yeah.
是的。
She thinks that Joey is actually Dr. Drake Ramore.
她認為喬伊實際上是德雷克·拉莫爾博士。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
I mean, and he's going out with her.
我是說，他要跟她出去。
He cannot pursue this.
他不能追求這個。
Hey, just because this woman thinks she can actually see Joey through the
嘿，只是因為這個女人認為她實際上可以透過窗戶看到喬伊
magical box in her living room doesn't mean she's not a person.
她客廳裡有一個神奇的盒子並不意味著她不是一個人。
I mean, does she not deserve happiness?
我的意思是，她不值得幸福嗎？
Does she not deserve love?
她不值得愛嗎？
What are you looking at me for?
你看著我幹什麼？
He's the one who wants to bop the maniac.
他就是那個想要打敗這個瘋子的人。
Are you okay?
你還好嗎？
No, uh-uh.
不，呃呃。
I'm just, I'm nervous.
我只是，我很緊張。
So, you know, maybe if I just, if I picture them all in
所以，你知道，也許如果我把它們全部想象出來
their underwear.
他們的內衣。
That's not a good idea.
這不是一個好主意。
That's kind of the reason the last guy got fired.
這就是最後一個人被解僱的原因。
I'm just, I'm, I'm, I'm used to playing for grown-ups.
我只是，我，我，我習慣了為大人打球。
You know, and they just, grown-ups drink their coffee and do their
你知道，他們只是，大人喝咖啡，做他們的事
grown-up thing, you know?
成年人的事，你知道嗎？
And kids, listen.
孩子們，聽著。
That's, it's just a huge responsibility.
也就是說，這只是一個巨大的責任。
What?
什麼？
Are you gonna kiss me?
你要吻我嗎？
I was thinking about it.
我正在想。
Okay.
好的。
Okay, all righty, let's play some tunes.
好吧，好吧，讓我們演奏一些曲子。
Okay, let's go find our seats.
好吧，我們去找座位吧。
Chandler, we're gonna find our seats.
錢德，我們要找到座位了。
Hold on a second.
等一下。
He thinks he can.
他認為他可以。
Oh, what the hell.
哦，到底是什麼。
He can.
他可以。
Hi, everybody, I'm Phoebe.
大家好，我是菲比。
Hi, Phoebe.
嗨，菲比。
Okay, um...
好吧，嗯...
I'm gonna play, um, some songs about grandparents, okay?
我要播放一些關於祖父母的歌曲，好嗎？
Now, Grandma's a person who everyone likes She bought you a train and
現在，奶奶是一個人人都喜歡的人，她買了火車，
a bright, shiny bike But lately she hasn't been coming to dinner And
一輛明亮閃亮的腳踏車但最近她沒有來吃晚餐而且
last time you saw her, she looked so much thinner Now, your mom
上次你見到她時，她看起來瘦了很多，現在，你媽媽
and your dad said she moved to Peru But the truth is she
你爸爸說她搬到秘魯 但事實是她
died and someday you will, too La-la-la-la-la-la-la
死了，有一天你也會死啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la La-la-la-la
啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦
-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la
I'll have the, um, grilled salmon and the doctor.
我要，嗯，烤鮭魚和醫生。
We'll have the risotto.
我們要吃義大利調味飯。
Thank you.
謝謝。
Oh, Drake, isn't it amazing?
哦，德雷克，這不是很神奇嗎？
Yeah, it is.
是的，確實如此。
What?
什麼？
I mean, here we sit, devil may care And just a little while
我的意思是，我們坐在這裡，魔鬼可能會關心，就一會兒
ago you were reattaching Simone's spinal cord.
在你重新連線西蒙娜的脊髓之前
Yeah, that was a tricky one.
是的，那是一個棘手的問題。
In reality, that operation takes, like, over ten hours But they only showed
事實上，那個手術需要十幾個小時 但他們只表明
it for two minutes.
兩分鐘。
Who's they?
他們是誰？
No one.
沒有人。
Oh, Drake, you are so talented.
哦，德雷克，你太有才華了。
Let me see those hands.
讓我看看那雙手。
Oh, these hands, these beautiful hands.
哦，這雙手，這雙美麗的雙手。
Oh, I could just eat them.
哦，我可以吃掉它們。
But I won't.
但我不會。
Otherwise my watch would fall off.
不然我的手錶就會掉下來。
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha Ha-ha-ha-ha
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
-ha-ha-ha-ha No, seriously.
-哈哈哈哈不，說真的。
These hands, these miracle, magical, life-giving hands Oh, just to be near
這些手，這些奇蹟般的、神奇的、賦予生命的手哦，只要靠近
them, touch them, maybe even lick one.
觸控它們，甚至舔它們。
All right, just one.
好吧，就一個。
Wow, you're good at that.
哇，你很擅長這件事。
Oh, my God, someone, he's choking.
哦，天哪，有人，他窒息了。
Is anyone here a doctor?
這裡有人是醫生嗎？
Oh, yes, yes, the best doctor in all of Salem.
哦，是的，是的，塞勒姆最好的醫生。
Dr. Drake Remore.
德雷克·雷摩爾博士。
Meet me in the nocturnal house in 15 minutes.
15 分鐘後在夜行屋見我。
Uh, hey, look, I don't really enjoy being with other men that way.
呃，嘿，聽著，我真的不喜歡這樣跟其他男人在一起。
But, um, Zoo Dollars?
但是，嗯，動物園幣？
It's about your monkey.
是關於你的猴子的。
It's alive.
它還活著。
I don't understand.
我不明白。
Why did you help that man?
為什麼要幫助那個人？
Uh, because, uh, I'm a neurosurgeon and that was clearly a case of,
呃，因為，呃，我是神經外科醫生，這顯然是一個案例，
uh, uh, foodal chokage.
呃，呃，食物窒息。
All right, look, I gotta tell you something.
好吧，聽著，我得告訴你一件事。
No, no, no, no, no.
不，不，不，不，不。
You don't have to tell me anything.
你不必告訴我任何事。
You don't have to explain yourself to me.
你不必向我解釋你自己。
Oh, who am I to question the great Dr. Drake Remore?
哦，我有什麼資格質疑偉大的德雷克·雷莫爾博士？
I should just be happy to be near you.
我應該很高興能靠近你。
Hey, I...
嘿，我...
Hey what?
嘿什麼？
That's it.
就是這樣。
Just hey.
只是嘿。
Like at the end of a dance.
就像在舞蹈結束時一樣。
Hey!
嘿！
Hey.
嘿。
There'll be times when you get older when you'll want to sleep with
有時候，當你變老的時候，你會想跟別人一起睡覺
people just to make them like you.
人們只是為了讓他們喜歡你。
But don't!
但不要！
Because that's another thing that you don't want to do.
因為那是另一件你不想做的事。
Everybody!
大家！
That's another thing that you don't want to do.
這是另一件你不想做的事情。
Excellent!
出色的！
Very informative!
資訊非常豐富！
Not at all inappropriate!
一點也不合適！
Thank you for coming, everybody.
謝謝大家的到來。
There are cookies in the back.
後面還有餅乾。
That was great.
那很棒。
The kids loved you.
孩子們愛你。
Yay.
耶。
I rock.
我搖滾。
And you know why?
你知道為什麼嗎？
Because you told the truth.
因為你說的是實話。
And nobody ever tells kids the truth.
沒有人告訴孩子真相。
You were incredible.
你太不可思議了。
But...
但是...
How did you know there was a but?
你怎麼知道有一個但是？
I sense these things.
我感覺到這些事。
It was either but or butter.
要嘛是但是，要嘛是黃油。
The thing is, I think, you know, some of the parents they were
問題是，我想，你知道，他們中的一些父母
kind of hoping that you'd play more songs about, like, barnyard animals.
有點希望你能播放更多關於農場動物之類的歌曲。
I can do that.
我能做到。
Really?
真的嗎？
Yeah.
是的。
Because that would be fantastic.
因為那太棒了。
What?
什麼？
You want to kiss me?
你想吻我嗎？
I'm thinking about it.
我正在考慮。
Okay, so if I get a library card, can I take you out
好的，如果我有借書卡，我可以帶你出去嗎
sometime?
某個時候？
What?
什麼？
I'm unemployed.
我失業了。
Ah, the bat.
啊，蝙蝠。
Ambassador of darkness.
黑暗大使。
Flitting out of his cave like a winged messenger.
就像長著翅膀的使者一樣，從他的洞穴裡飛了出來。
Sightless specter of the macabre.
看不見的可怕幽靈。
Buddy, my monkey.
夥計，我的猴子。
Oh, yeah, right.
哦，是的，沒錯。
There was a break in a few months back.
幾個月前有一次休息。
Inside job.
內部工作。
Your monkey was taken.
你的猴子被帶走了。
Along with a snowy egret, a two-toed sloth, and three hooded sweatshirts
還有一隻雪鷺、一隻二趾樹懶和三件連帽運動衫
from the zoo gift shop.
從動物園禮品店買的。
Oh, my God, but the zoo told me my monkey was dead.
哦，天哪，但是動物園告訴我我的猴子死了。
The zoo.
動物園。
Do you believe everything the zoo tells you?
你相信動物園告訴你的一切嗎？
That's the only thing the zoo's ever told me.
這是動物園唯一告訴我的事。
Of course they're going to say he's dead.
他們當然會說他死了。
They don't want the bad publicity.
他們不要負面的宣傳。
It's all a great big cover-up.
這都是一個巨大的掩蓋。
Do you have any idea how high up this thing goes?
你知道這東西有多高嗎？
That guy Lipson?
利普森那個人？
Lipson knows.
利普森知道。
Do you have any idea who else knows?
你知道還有誰知道嗎？
No, I only know Lipson.
不，我只認識利普森。
Hmm.
唔。
Lipson knows, huh?
利普森知道吧？
Ah, hello, Mr. Possum.
啊，你好，負鼠先生。
Enigma of the trees.
樹木之謎。
Upside-down denizen of the night.
顛倒的夜晚居民。
Taunting gravity.
嘲諷重力。
Buddy, my monkey.
夥計，我的猴子。
My monkey.
我的猴子。
Word on the street.
街上有話。
Well, when I say street, I mean those little pretend streets they have
好吧，當我說街道時，我指的是那些假裝的小街道
here at the zoo.
在動物園這裡。
Of course.
當然。
Your monkey found a new career in the entertainment field.
你的猴子在娛樂領域找到了新的職業。
That's all I know.
我只知道這些。
This is unbelievable.
這太令人難以置信了。
So, what is this information worth to you, my friend?
那麼，我的朋友，這些資訊對你來說有什麼價值呢？
Are you trying to get me to bribe you?
你是想讓我賄賂你嗎？
Maybe.
或許。
But you already told me everything.
但你已經告訴我一切了。
Check it out.
一探究竟。
He actually is the monkey-shine monkey.
他其實是一隻猴子。
Oh, wow.
哦，哇。
Well, so what are you gonna do?
好吧，那你要做什麼？
Well, I guess I'm gonna call the beer company and try to find
好吧，我想我要打電話給啤酒公司並嘗試找到
out where he is.
知道他在哪裡。
That's what I did when I lost my client's tails.
當我失去客戶的尾巴時，我就是這麼做的。
Okay, hi again.
好吧，又嗨了。
Hi!
你好！
Today, we're gonna start with some songs about barnyard animals.
今天，我們將從一些關於農場動物的歌曲開始。
Oh, the cow in the meadow goes moo Oh, the cow in the
哦，草地上的牛哞哞叫 哦，草地上的牛
meadow goes moo Then the farmer hits him on the head and grinds
草地發出哞哞聲 然後農夫敲打他的頭並磨碎
him up And that's how we get hamburgers Now, chicken!
他起來 這就是我們吃漢堡的方法 現在，雞肉！
You're the only one who can save her, Drake.
你是唯一能救她的人，德雷克。
Dammit, I'm a doctor.
該死，我是醫生。
I'm not God.
我不是上帝。
Well, there goes my whole belief system.
好吧，我的整個信仰體係都消失了。
It's Erica.
是艾麗卡。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Quick, shut off the TV.
快點關掉電視。
No, no, no, wait.
不不不，等等。
I want to see what happens.
我想看看會發生什麼事。
Uh, I get Leslie out of the coma, and then we make out.
呃，我把萊斯利從昏迷中喚醒，然後我們就親熱了。
How can that be?
怎麼可能呢？
You were just kissing Sabrina.
你剛剛在親吻薩布麗娜。
Rachel, it's a world where Joey is a neurosurgeon.
瑞秋，在這個世界裡，喬伊是一名神經外科醫生。
Hey, Erica.
嘿，艾麗卡。
Come on in.
進來吧。
How did you get here so fast?
你怎麼這麼快就到了這裡？
I just saw you in Salem.
我剛剛在塞勒姆見到你。
Right, they, uh, they choppered me in.
是的，他們，呃，他們把我砍了。
What's up?
這是怎麼回事？
Oh, and I see you're having a little party, too.
哦，我發現你也在舉辦一個小型聚會。
Is she here?
她在嗎？
Huh?
啊？
Who?
WHO？
Sabrina.
薩布麗娜.
I know about you two.
我知道你們兩個。
I saw you today kissing in the doctor's lounge.
我今天看到你在醫生休息室接吻。
That's not what you think.
那不是你想的那樣。
That was...
那是...
You told me I was the only one.
你告訴我我是唯一的一個。
All right, look, that's it.
好吧，你看，就是這樣。
I don't think we should see each other anymore, all right?
我想我們不該再見面了，好嗎？
Look, I know I should have told you this a long time ago,
聽著，我知道我早就該告訴你這件事了
but I am not Drake Ramore, okay?
但我不是德雷克·拉莫爾，好嗎？
I'm not even a doctor.
我甚至不是醫生。
I'm an actor.
我是一名演員。
I just pretend to be a doctor.
我只是假裝自己是醫生。
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
Do the people at the hospital know about this?
醫院裡的人知道這件事嗎？
Somebody want to help me out here?
有人想幫我嗎？
Oh, I know.
哦，我知道。
I know.
我知道。
Where am I?
我在哪裡？
University Hospital.
大學醫院。
The same place you've been for the last 18 years.
過去 18 年你一直待在同一個地方。
How...
怎麼...
How can you be here and there?
你怎麼能在這裡或那裡？
Because it's a television show.
因為這是電視劇。
Drake, what are you getting at?
德雷克，你想說什麼？
Nice girl.
好女孩。
Not great with concepts.
概念不太好。
I'm not Drake.
我不是德雷克。
That's right.
這是正確的。
He's not Drake.
他不是德雷克。
He's Hans Ramore, Drake's evil twin.
他是漢斯·拉莫爾，德雷克的邪惡雙胞胎。
Is this true?
這是真的嗎？
Yes.
是的。
Yes, it is true.
是的，確實如此。
And I know this because...
我知道這一點是因為...
because he pretended to be Drake to...
因為他假裝是德雷克...
to sleep with me.
和我一起睡。
What?
什麼？
And then he told me he would run away with me.
然後他告訴我他會跟我私奔。
And he didn't!
但他沒有！
And you left the toilet seat up, you bastard!
你還把馬桶座圈開啟了，你這個混蛋！
Is all this true?
這一切都是真的嗎？
Yes.
是的。
I'm afraid it is.
恐怕是的。
You deserve much better than me, Erica.
你值得比我更好，艾麗卡。
You deserve to be with the real Drake.
你值得和真正的德雷克在一起。
He's the one you fell in love with.
他就是你愛上的那個人。
Go to Salem.
去塞勒姆。
Find him.
找到他。
He's the guy for you.
他就是適合你的人。
Oh, Hans.
哦，漢斯。
Hans?
漢斯？
Hans.
漢斯.
Your evil twin.
你邪惡的雙胞胎。
Right.
正確的。
Goodbye, Erica.
再見，艾麗卡。
Good luck in Salem.
祝你在塞勒姆好運。
Take care.
小心。
I'll never forget you, Hans.
我永遠不會忘記你，漢斯。
All right.
好的。
The people who threw the water.
那些潑水的人。
I'll clean you out.
我會把你清理掉。
Fired?
被解僱？
Why?
為什麼？
The library board has had a lot of complaints from parents about some
圖書館董事會收到了許多家長的投訴
of the stuff in your songs.
你歌曲中的東西。
I can't believe this is the library, you know?
我不敢相信這是圖書館，你知道嗎？
I mean, books, free speech, you know, newspapers on sticks.
我的意思是，書籍、言論自由，你知道，報紙。
I know.
我知道。
I mean, and what about the kids, you know?
我的意思是，那孩子呢，你知道嗎？
Did you tell your board about how the kids want to hear the
您是否告訴董事會孩子們希望如何聽到
truth?
真相？
No.
不。
I see.
我懂了。
Maybe if you just played some regular kiddie songs.
也許如果你只是播放一些普通的兒童歌曲。
No.
不。
What do you want me to be?
你想讓我成為什麼？
Like some stupid, big, like, purple dinosaur?
就像一些愚蠢的、大的、紫色的恐龍？
I'm not saying you have to be Barney.
我並不是說你必須是巴尼。
Who's Barney?
巴尼是誰？
Hey, you're never gonna believe this.
嘿，你永遠不會相信這一點。
Ooh, let me guess.
哦，讓我猜一下。
What?
什麼？
Some weebles actually do fall down?
有些蛆蟲真的會掉下來嗎？
Huh?
啊？
A stitch in time now only saves seven?
現在及時縫一針只能省七針？
What do you got?
你有什麼？
Huh.
呵呵。
Never mind.
沒關係。
What?
什麼？
Well, I tracked down Marcel, and get this.
好吧，我找到了馬塞爾，並得到了這個。
He's healthy, he's happy, and he's right here in New York filming Outbreak
他很健康，他很快樂，而且他正在紐約拍攝《爆發》
2, The Virus Takes Manhattan.
2、病毒佔領曼哈頓。
You're kidding!
你開玩笑吧！
Oh, my God.
我的天啊。
This is amazing.
這太棒了。
I know.
我知道。
I finally get a part on TV, and the monkey's making movies.
我終於在電視上得到了一個角色，猴子也開始拍電影了。
Okay, Rachel, I'm ready.
好的，雷切爾，我準備好了。
Okay.
好的。
Excuse me.
打擾一下。
Is this where the singing lady is who tells the truth?
這就是說實話的歌女嗎？
Um, yeah, I guess that's me.
嗯，是的，我想那就是我。
She's here!
她來了！
Sometimes men love women And sometimes men love men And then there are
有時男人愛女人 有時男人愛男人 然後還有
bisexual men And then there are bisexuals Though some just say they're kidding
雙性戀男人 然後還有雙性戀 雖然有些人只是說他們在開玩笑
themselves La-la-la-la, la-la-la-la La-la-la-la,
他們自己啦啦啦啦，啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦啦，